If you're an Airtel customer, you're in for a treat.
This company has transformed the future of all its
customers. Airtel
Payments Bank has launched its
first-ever customer
health care insurance facility to provide easy health insurance to customers.
Airtel has also entered into a
corporate agency agreement with Care Health and Insurance.
These health insurance
products range from ₹50,000 to ₹5 lakh, offering
numerous other benefits, including comprehensive
health care treatment for all existing illnesses.
Customers will receive customized and
comprehensive 360-degree health insurance, along with
Airtel Thanks Up's
highly comfortable banking
experience. This health care
financially assures policyholders of quality health care in case of any
medical emergency.
Customers
can enroll in this health insurance scheme easily and simply.
Customers can use their Airtel Payments Bank account on Airtel Thanks Up
and make a payment through a net bank or other bank account.  You can
buy this health insurance by making payment through debit card. Airtel has tied up with Care Health Insurance to provide a
wide range of health insurance to its customers. This will
provide health insurance to millions of customers who either do
not have insurance or have a minimum insurance cover with the help of digitally rich and present network distribution. So,
if you are also an Airtel customer, then
you can quickly buy this new insurance for yourself and your
family.
[Music]
[Prasha]